(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2=
Art is the soul of Paris.
For centuries,
Paris has always stood at
the forefront of humanity's
aesthetics and creativity.
From the classic paintings
of the Renaissance
to the Impressionists' exploration
of light and shadow,
this city
has witnessed the evolution
of global art,
preserving the most touching expressions
of human civilization.
Today,
the Earth Group,
in this world capital of art,
will tour the Louvre,
meet timeless artworks
spanning centuries,
turn into painting figures,
step out of the canvases
and kick off a brand-new,
wonderful artistic adventure.
=Episode 7 (Part 1)=
(Magical Night at the Paris Museum)
Morning.
(Song Qian)
Such a lovely day.
Good morning.
Hello.
Your outfits match perfectly.
Yeah.
Mustard yellow on you.
(Today's OOTD)
Mustard yellow.
Yeah.
It's mustard yellow.
(So yellow)
So yellow.
Mustard yellow.
Why?
Can't it be mustard yellow?
No, I meant "so".
So.
So yellow.
Why is it so yellow?
(That's so cringey)
Are you correcting your senior's
word stress?
Why is it so yellow?
Why are you so purple?
Morning, Yuning.
Morning.
I saw a video today
where they were playing a game
called
Who Got Shot.
I got shot.
Yeah.
Why?
I got it.
(Figured it out in a second)
I got the logic right away.
(Observing intently)
Who got shot?
He's totally confused.
Him.
He got shot.
Why?
I got it.
You got it, right?
You even got it?
It's like "Black Magic". One more time.
Come on.
Me, right?
Yes, it's you.
Why?
No.
How did you get it?
Why?
- Haven't you figured out the logic yet?
- I'm so smart.
- I get it now.
- No.
Everyone, be quiet. Do it one more time.
Who got shot?
You.
You got shot.
(Still confused)
Still don't get it?
Why?
(Not telling you)
(Go figure it out yourself)
Hahahahaha.
(Your laugh is so hurtful)
(I want to escape)
Let's go, get in the car.
Get in the car.
We're heading to the Louvre.
No way, this gaming is so...
(Heading to the Louvre)
I'm wearing purple today.
- No wonder.
- Do you have other outfits?
I do, but...
why not wear them?
Because I can layer a sweater
under this.
Yesterday, I almost texted you
to borrow one of your clothes.
No.
I'm deleting you right now.
(You are not friends with him)
You could have deleted me
the moment he grabbed the ball.
(Arriving at the destination)
Come on, we're here.
Let's go.
(Li Naiwen)
Hello.
(Guo Jingfei)
Today is perfect.
Good afternoon.
We meet again.
Hello.
(Zu Lishu,
Official docent of French museums)
Let's go this way.
So handsome.
(Sun Honglei)
This tourist is so cooperative.
Yeah.
(Maizi,
Certified French National Museum Guide)
Good morning, everyone.
Today, we are going to visit
France's museum,
Louvre.
(Louvre, built in 1204, houses over 400,000 artworks)
The Louvre Museum consists of
(One of the world's oldest, largest, and most famous museums)
a three-winged building complex.
(Ranking first among the world's four major museums)
This plaza, or this roundabout,
is Place du Carrousel.
From this square,
we can get the clearest view
of this building.
This is actually a gate,
known as the Little Arc de Triomphe,
or the Arc de Triomphe du Carrousel.
And this glass pyramid in the center,
(The Louvre Pyramid, completed in 1989)
in the early 1980s,
(It reflects skylight through glass and provides daylight for underground facilities)
was commissioned by French President Mitterrand
(Solving challenges in modernizing the historic palace)
for the Louvre's expansion.
It was designed
by the Chinese-American architect,
I. M. Pei.
Now, it is one of
Paris's key landmarks.
Let's walk inside.
We're at the tip of the pyramid.
So beautiful.
Gorgeous.
This is
the glass structure we saw from outside.
Yes.
That pyramid.
The building
I'm pointing to
(France's former Ministry of Finance)
used to house French Ministry of Finance.
In 1981,
a new Minister of Culture took office.
He proposed
relocating the Ministry of Finance
to return the building to the Louvre
as an expanded exhibition hall.
So, President Mitterrand
readily approved the plan.
And
I. M. Pei was selected.
(I. M. Pei born in Guangzhou, Guangdong)
His design proposal
(A foreign member of the Chinese Academy of Engineering, a Pritzker Architecture Prize laureate)
faced a lot of skepticism at first,
(A world-renowned master architect)
but the final work was masterfully executed,
(Regarded as an icon of modernist architecture in academic circle)
blending historic architecture with modern design seamlessly.
(His works feature a perfect blend of modern innovation and Chinese culture)
There are five pyramids in total,
all shaped as regular square pyramids
standing 21.6 meters tall.
Their load-bearing frames
are stainless steel,
with 673 custom
ultra-clear glass panels.
(Footage sourced online)
Among the five pyramids, the largest serves as the main entrance.
(The Great Pyramid, In the center of the square, Main visitor entrance)
Near the elevators,
the three small pyramids
(Three Small Pyramids, Entrances to exhibition halls)
lead to three exhibition halls.
(Inverted Pyramid, Underground Skylight)
And an inverted pyramid
acts as an underground skylight.
The Louvre Museum,
according to incomplete statistics,
now
holds over 400,000 collections.
So many.
It displays 40,000 artworks
spanning
ancient civilizations
to the mid-19th century.
Today, we will visit
the Venus de Milo,
the Winged Victory of Samothrace,
and the Mona Lisa,
the Louvre's Three Great Treasures,
as well as the Code of Hammurabi.
We're now in
the Richelieu Wing,
one of the three main wings
of the Louvre.
We all know that
one of the earliest origins
of human civilization
lies on
somewhere we all know,
the Mesopotamian Plain,
with a history of over 6,000 years.
So, for the Mesopotamian Plain.
When we talk about
the Mesopotamian Plain
and Mesopotamia,
what comes to your mind?
King Hammurabi of Old Babylonian
issued the Code of Hammurabi.
The Code of Hammurabi,
completed around 1700 BC,
over 3,700 years ago,
stands right
at the entrance of the Mesopotamia
exhibition hall we're heading to.
Walk through this door,
and we'll see
the Code of Hammurabi.
(The Code of Hammurabi was promulgated around 1776 BC by Hammurabi)
The Code of Hammurabi
(The King of Old Babylon in the Middle East)
dates back more than 3,700 years.
(It's the most representative cuneiform legal code)
It is the world's most intact surviving
(And the world's first relatively complete written law code)
early written code of laws.
It is carved
on a solid black basalt stele.
All inscriptions
on the stele
are cuneiform.
This text...
You need a magnifying glass
to see them clearly.
Yeah.
Two figures are carved on the stele.
Can you guess which one is
the King of Old Babylon,
Hammurabi?
The seated one.
The seated one is Hammurabi, right?
Seated there,
the king exudes great majesty,
so you can tell
it's Hammurabi.
Actually, that's wrong.
(King of Old Babylon, Hammurabi)
The one standing is Hammurabi.
And the seated one is Shamash.
(Sun God, Shamash)
The god of the sun at that time.
This means
he wanted to show
all that
his power to make laws
(Content generated by AI)
comes from the god.
The god granted me this scepter,
empowering me
to inscribe this code.
Very beautiful.
The stele
bears 282 legal provisions
covering many interesting cases,
such as divorce, property,
and civil disputes
in full detail.
It is like a book.
Follow me, everyone.
I'll show you
the oldest sculpture in the Louvre.
Among the Louvre's 40,000 exhibits,
the latest works
date to the mid-19th century,
while the oldest sculpture here
is over 9,000 years old,
actually.
(Unearthed in 1985 at the Ain Ghazal site in Jordan)
This is the Ain Ghazal Statue,
(One of the earliest surviving large intact human statues)
unearthed in present-day Jordan.
(And the oldest artifact on display at the Louvre)
It even has its hands in its pockets.
No, its arms are lost.
And it's hollow inside.
You can understand it that way.
Look at its eyeliner.
Its eye lines are exquisitely painted.
Made of natural bitumen.
Way better than Fei's eye makeup.
(This is a negative review)
So, was it made by ordinary people?
Made by ordinary people.
That era was still the Neolithic Age.
It's quite vivid.
Very vivid.
Look, it's exquisitely crafted.
Back in that era, people were already
experimenting with makeup.
Yeah.
I said it's way better
than Fei's eye makeup.
Yeah.
Ahead of us,
you'll see
the Great Sphinx of Tanis.
(The Great Sphinx of Tanis, often simply called the Louvre Sphinx)
Turn right directly to the Ancient Greek Sculpture Hall.
(It was carved from rose granite, unearthed at
the Temple of Tanis in Egypt, about over 4,000 years old)
(The human face represents the pharaoh, the lion body symbolizes protective power,
making it a classic sculpture blending ancient Egyptian kingship and divinity)
All the sculptures we're seeing now
(Athena of Velletri)
are ancient Greek artworks
(A Roman marble sculpture depicting)
from the Classical period.
(The goddess of wisdom and war, Athena)
Everyone, come over here.
Look, all these standing statues
rest weight on one leg
and relax the other.
Humans can stand freely on both legs,
yet stones lack structural stability.
That explains the large stone
support next to every statue's legs.
It's the same logic
as the figure collectibles
we bought.
So, it's just to prop it up.
There's a support.
There's a support point.
Yeah.
Don't you also need a support point
when taking photos?
Yeah.
Acting also needs a support point.
The Venus de Milo.
Why is it so precious?
Its own contrapposto balance
is perfect.
Everyone, follow me closely.
You'll understand it now if we
analyze it from three perspectives.
Mechanics, mathematics and aesthetics.
When admiring this treasure
of the museum,
you'll figure out why it
stands out
and is so unique among all artworks.
Honglei.
The Venus de Milo.
Venus.
(The Venus de Milo, also known as
the Armless Venus, a marble sculpture created by the ancient Greek sculptor Alexandros)
(Around 150 BC. It is one of
the Louvre's Three Great Treasures)
The Venus de Milo,
the top treasure
of the Louvre.
It stands
2.04 meters tall.
Created by the ancient Greek sculptor,
Alexandros,
around 150 BC.
The statue is assembled from two pieces
of white marble,
portraying the Greek goddess
of love and beauty,
Venus.
Observe its aesthetic details closely.
Have you noticed the lines carved
on her neck?
Yes.
The necklines are so realistic.
And her facial proportions
follow the ancient Greek
aesthetic standards.
The length of the face is three times
that of the nose.
The entire body
forms an elegant S-curve,
with perfectly balanced proportions,
showing us
what the Greeks valued in beauty
over 2,000 years ago.
It is widely regarded
as the most beautiful
surviving ancient Greek female statue
ever discovered.
Let's move on to
the Louvre's second top treasure,
the Winged Victory of Samothrace.
Stand where we are
and look up at the steps to your left.
(The Winged Victory of Samothrace is the pinnacle
of the Hellenistic new sculptural movement)
(Created around 200 BC)
The sculpture up there
(To commemorate the naval victory off the island of Samothrace)
is the Louvre's second great treasure,
(One of the Louvre's Three Great Treasures)
the Winged Victory Samothrace.
The base of this statue
is carved in the shape
of a warship's bow.
The Winged Victory stands atop it,
as if leading the fleet through
stormy waves.
As visitors walk up the stairs,
their eyes create
an illusion of swaying on the sea,
fully reflecting
the original intention
of honoring the naval triumph.
The Winged Victory of Samothrace
earned its status
as a Louvre treasure
due to its profound symbolic meaning
for the French people.
The statue
depicts
Nike,
the Greek goddess of victory,
whose image aligns perfectly with
France's long-standing reverence
for glory and triumph.
This spirit
echoes the core ideas
embodied by
iconic French landmarks
such as the Paris Arc de Triomphe
and the Marianne statue.
There is
an ideal viewing spot.
The platform on your right,
around this position.
(The line of sight forms a 45-degree angle with the statue)
From here, you can admire
its stunning curved silhouette,
defined musculature,
wind-blown robes,
and every intricate fold on the garment
in full view.
So beautiful.
Let's keep moving forward.
Now, we are leaving the Greek period,
the Ancient Greek era,
and heading into
the Italian Painting Gallery.
Amazing.
This is the final section
of our tour today.
This part is the Louvre's
(The Grande Galerie of the Louvre)
largest
(First constructed under Henry IV in 1959)
and the longest gallery,
(Transformed into public museum in 1793)
known as the Grande Galerie.
(The first area opened to the public)
It was the riverside corridor
(In the 19th century, a glass dome was added to illuminate the paintings with natural light)
built during the reign of Henry IV.
(It houses an extensive collection of Italian Renaissance art,
featuring masterpieces by great artists including Da Vinci, Raffaello)
Every artwork displayed in this hall
ranges
from the Renaissance
to
the paintings of the 17th
and 18th centuries.
Let's take a look at this painting.
The Virgin of the Rocks
by Leonardo da Vinci.
(Virgin of the Rocks by Leonardo da Vinci)
Virgin of the Rocks.
- Here, this one.
- That's right.
About this Virgin of the Rocks,
when Leonardo da Vinci was 31 years old,
he painted this work for the church.
The angel has no wings.
The Madonna has no halo.
Saint John has no cross.
The church members were furious.
They couldn't understand
what he painted at all.
Leonardo da Vinci said,
"I put all my heart into it,
but you don't know how to appreciate it.
If you want me to add them,
you have to pay me more."
Leonardo da Vinci was taken to court.
Left with no choice, he painted
a substitute version for them.
It's in the UK.
(The second version of Virgin of the Rocks
is now in the National Gallery, London)
(Comparison of the two versions)
The angel has white wings,
the Madonna is wearing
a golden little circle,
and Saint John has a cross.
See?
Everyone, follow me straight ahead.
Next, we are going to see
the most important treasure
of the Louvre,
the Mona Lisa.
(The Mona Lisa)
The Mona Lisa is right ahead.
Yeah.
(The Mona Lisa)
This painting.
Fantastic.
So magnificent.
The Mona Lisa is a work
by Leonardo da Vinci
that took over ten years to create.
It is the ultimate representative
of the humanistic spirit
of the Renaissance.
You can see over here
that there are three highlights.
First, the hands.
He could paint the muscles,
fascia, and nerves
all for you to see.
Second, the background.
(A hazy landscape background)
This landscape is fictional.
A winding mountain path on the left
and a small bridge
over flowing water on the right.
Higher on one side
and lower on the other.
Very mysterious.
And lastly,
(His unique sfumato technique)
the image has a soft-focus,
matte quality.
(The most beautiful building is built on time.
Time will give all the answers. - I.M. Pei)
- You nailed the look.
- You look so like her.
Yeah.
A chubbier version
of the Girl with a Pearl Earring.
You nailed it.
Just like her.
Yeah.
Here they come.
(A grand entrance)
That explains it.
The person sitting
next to you will find it prickly.
I thought
it was the Lion King.
He really looks so much
like the Lion King.
(Direct-from-producer sales)
- He's not even a person.
- Here, have some sunflower seeds.
You really should have prepared
some sunflower seeds in your pocket.
(Sunflower eating imaginary seeds)
Hello, all you masterpieces.
Today, we gather in Paris
(Chen Xingxu)
to participate in
this year's Magical Night in Paris:
Gathering of Masterpieces.
Please introduce yourselves, one by one.
- Start with the plant.
Start with the species.
Include my full body.
Why is there a shell behind?
This is a vase.
That is a vase.
My name is
Vase with Fifteen Sunflowers.
(Created in Arles, in Provence, southern France
by Dutch Impressionist Vincent van Gogh)
(One of the Sunflowers series of oil paintings)
Mr. Van Gogh spent his entire life
(Lin Yi)
creating 11 sunflower paintings.
Why are you looking at me?
(All eyes turned to him)
I've never seen a sunflower talk.
(Feeling special)
This is novel. Is that not allowed?
Eat some sunflower seeds.
(An oil painting by Leonardo da Vinci)
I am the Mona Lisa.
(An Italian Renaissance painter)
I am now one of the greatest treasures
(Now in the Louvre in Paris, France)
of the Louvre.
(One of the museum's treasures)
Yeah.
(Wang Yuwen)
Why are you looking at me like that?
(Liu Yuning)
The work
I represent...
What are you doing?
Reveal your true form?
(Adjusting his flowery clothes)
I'm a Sunflower Spirit.
Yes, the sunflower has come to life.
Maybe he wants some sunflower seeds.
(Young Man with an Apple, an oil painting
by the Italian Raffaello Sanzio, around 1500)
(Exhibited in China: Apr 28 to Aug 28, 2026)
The painter who created me
is called Raffaello.
I'm supposed to be on display
in Beijing.
But to cooperate
with the filming of Wow The World S2,
I flew from Beijing
to Paris specifically.
My schedule is very tight.
I hope you can film quickly.
After filming, I have to
catch a flight. Thank you.
Don't you usually go by sea freight?
Yes.
Yeah.
I get seasick.
Come on.
(The Fifer, an oil on canvas painting in 1866)
Hello, everyone.
(by the French Impressionist Édouard Manet)
I am The Fifer.
(Currently housed
in the Orsay Museum in Paris, France)
As you can see,
I must be a musician,
a figure
in a ceremonial guard
like that.
(I have a question)
Well,
why did Mr. Manet only paint you?
- No other members?
- Yeah.
Why?
Because...
I'm handsome!
Right.
You are a fifer,
not a boaster.
I can tell you're very boastful.
Because he can blow.
I am...
(Songwriter of Sailor)
Created by Mr. Zheng Zhihua.
Personally created by Mr. Zheng Zhihua.
(Trying to get back on track)
The famous, great artist...
Why don't you sing
your representative work,
Sailor?
Mr. Renoir
painted a portrait,
and I'm the man in the painting,
Fernand.
(Childhood of Fernand Halphen)
I was born into
(Created by a French Impressionist)
(Pierre-Auguste Renoir)
a wealthy middle-class family in Paris.
(Currently housed
in the Orsay Museum in Paris, France)
I've been passionate
about music since childhood.
(With a straight face)
♪He says, the pain in the storm♪
(Starts singing instantly)
There is
a ballad of mine
known to every household.
I see.
And...
the most famous line is...
(Reading mode on)
♪The pain in the storm is nothing♪
You even read it?
That is why I am dressed like this.
The role I am playing
is from a painting
created
(Harlequin and Pierrot by the French Fauvist)
by a very formidable Fauvist painter
(André Derain)
called André Derain.
(Currently in the Orangery Museum
in Paris, France)
Impressive.
Me.
(Searching...)
It wasn't spread by word of mouth,
So,
not everyone knows about this painting.
The name is too long.
It is called
Portrait of Baldassare Castiglione.
(An oil on canvas portrait created)
(by Italian Raffaello Sanzio in 1515)
It was painted by Raffaello.
(Currently housed
in the Louvre Museum in Paris, France)
He was one
of the most cultured gentlemen
of 16th-century Italy.
I am
the Girl with a Pearl Earring.
(Created by the Dutch Johannes Vermeer in 1665)
I was created in the 17th century
(Briefly exhibited at the Louvre)
by a Dutch painter
(Regarded as the Mona Lisa of the North)
named Johannes Vermeer.
(by the Dutch art critic Goschier)
This name was just casually given.
Just throwing a name together.
- This is like...
- Because it's true to its name.
Then this is the Big Fool
Wearing a Plaid Top?
This is the Old Man
Wearing a Chef's Hat.
♪I hear the sailor say♪
I have my own background music.
Young Lad in a Sailor Suit.
Isn't this the Young Man
Holding an Apple?
Masterpieces,
let's first recreate
the poses from your own paintings.
I can create my own, right?
Our understanding of sunflowers
is sunshine and positivity.
(Graceful hand gesture)
Good.
This sunflower
is seductive.
I have to respect myself.
Respect the original.
(Copycat)
Look.
She is just playing herself.
Good, not bad.
That's it.
(Automatically stretching)
(Hand details)
His expression.
(Trying to learn)
You nailed it.
He really looks like it
after pulling a long face.
I'm standing at ease.
Your pose.
At ease.
It's like this.
Bouncing down the mountain.
You nailed it.
You even dyed your eyebrows.
Really impressive.
I tell you, Qian,
the degree of your resemblance
is only second to the Sunflower.
(Harsh words hurt Honglei's feelings)
You nailed it.
You really look like the painting.
Very much.
So, next,
paintings,
you are about to embark on
The Great Art Escape.
The first mission
is to quietly escape from the frame.
Only by completing the mission
can you go to the outside world.
(Quietly escape from the frame)
Within ten minutes,
all members must escape
through different gaps in the frame.
There will be patrols in the museum.
If you hear the alarm sound,
you must strike your poses
in the paintings
before the alarm ends and take a photo.
If during this process,
the sound made exceeds 65 decibels,
or the bell rings,
the person currently passing through
needs to return and start over.
At the same time,
someone must accept the punishment.
A two-finger slap on the arm.
I'm afraid you'll hold us back.
My outfit is holding me back.
- And it'll hold you back.
- What do I do?
Mine is a disadvantage too.
It's okay. Let's...
Let's take it as it comes.
(Take it as it comes)
This is quite difficult.
If someone fails, they'll get slapped.
I'm telling you, Yuning.
(Discussing tactics)
This one and this one.
I can barely crawl through this one,
but it's very risky.
And this, we have to carry someone
and squeeze them through.
It's hard to move the guys over,
and some of them are pretty heavy.
Let's move the girls.
We'll split these lower ones.
I think we should let
Duke and Sunflower go through these two.
Okay.
Lin Yi goes through this one. He's thin.
What about me? I'll go through this.
Yes.
You go through this.
Yuning and Xingxu go through these two.
I'll go first.
(Go)
(Escape the frame)
Slow down.
(Panicked)
(The bell rings. The person has to start over)
Come back.
(Pulled back by force)
(The Sunflower is stuck)
There's a bell, Honglei.
You can't make the bell ring.
Punishment.
(Such a solid hit)
(Start over again)
(Adjusting posture)
(The line is pressed against him)
Haha!
(Progress 1/8)
(Impressive)
This one.
(Duke's exit)
(Without hesitation)
(Everyone comes to help)
Lower your head.
(Tell me earlier)
(Lowering his head)
(All-around protection)
Your butt.
(Progress 2/8)
You crawl through this one.
(Guo Jingfei's exit)
Wrap it tight.
(Successfully got one leg out)
Attention.
(Strike your pose when the alarm sounds)
The patrol is starting soon.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
(More than half of his body is out)
Come back from the side.
(Succeed?)
(Failed at the last moment)
(Quick restart)
Get ready.
Come on.
First, step your foot over.
(What a familiar process)
Your head.
Head through, good.
Follow my hand.
(Too scared to move)
Okay.
Your leg.
Be careful.
(Progress 3/8)
Me?
(Next one)
(Wang Yuwen's exit)
(Folding the dress)
What should I do?
Face up.
Do you want it face up or face down?
(Tactic: Go through face‑up)
Face up.
(Stiffly)
Attention.
The patrol is starting soon.
Three.
Two.
One.
(Let go of his hand)
(Let go of his hand?)
(Didn't forget to stretch his face)
(Weight increases)
(Straining arms)
Put her down first.
Wait a moment.
Okay, it's fine.
No need.
(Didn't forget punishment)
Well...
Don't let go.
I won't.
Because Naiwen just did it like this.
(Witnessed the whole thing)
My apple.
Is the apple more important
or the person?
(Isn't this obvious enough?)
(Got it)
Come on.
Hurry.
(Holding breath)
(Progress 4/8)
(Running out of energy)
Okay, next one.
Next.
(Next one)
Qian.
Come on.
(The headpiece got caught)
What is this?
(Tired)
This thing hung down.
She's getting mad.
(Holding it in her mouth)
(Holding it in his mouth. Ready to help)
(The big three are still going strong)
Okay?
Take a breath.
Go.
(Gritting teeth and persevering)
(Let me help you!)
(Being more of a hindrance than a help)
It's fine.
(Let's do it again in one breath)
Three, go.
(Coming to help again)
Go.
(Naiwen's clothes touched it again)
Get her down first.
Down.
Put her down first.
Put her down.
(Looking pitiful)
Put her down first.
Who?
Don't touch it.
You.
(Full responsibility for this round)
Go to the back.
His cloak.
(The cloak is fully responsible)
(The three who bore it all)
Wait, let me take a rest.
My hands. So tired.
Let's switch.
No, I'm tall. I'll use my shoulder.
(Having a new idea)
Someone lift me up.
- Then someone catch me over there.
- We can all lift you up.
(New plan: Head first)
Then I can hug you.
Then you push my legs through.
Okay, come on, go.
(The laborers are back to work)
Who can lift me up?
Come on, one, two, three.
(Catching up)
No.
It's fine. Get down first.
Get down first.
Not like that.
(Again)
(The three of them are back at it)
Come on.
Okay.
Pull me over.
(Gradually raising)
(Uneven: Guo Jingfei's listed height is 180 cm,
while their average height is 187 cm)
(Gradually putting pressure
on the other side)
No, go forward.
(Not tall enough, using his head)
Fei, don't push with your head.
You hold me.
(The bell rings)
Don't push me with your head.
(You think I want to do it?)
You lift me up like this
so that I can hold onto you,
and get down.
I don't have that much strength.
Maybe we need someone taller.
Who was just useless?
"Who was just useless?"
I'll go.
You have to go through from this.
You can't just go straight over.
(Must go through the frame)
Is it not allowed?
No.
(Trapped by the height problem)
(Time's up. Mission failed)
Time's up. First round failed.
Actually, you broke the rules too.
Be careful next round.
It's fine.
Can't get past it.
I think we should
let a tall guy go first.
(Tactic adjusts: A tall guy leads the way)
Lin Yi or Xingxu go first.
Yes.
Lin Yi, give it a try.
Pull your pants up a bit.
(Lin Yi tries)
He's tall.
He has long legs.
His head is okay.
Your shoulders.
Shrink your shoulders.
After you get over, jump.
Jump over.
Your bottom!
This is too curvy.
(Find it too graceful)
Too graceful.
Well, the left half is through.
But the right half...
You touched it.
Also,
buddies,
one person is enough.
When it rang just now,
the people behind started clapping.
(Let the audience hear the sound)
Those who go first
lash themselves, okay?
Okay.
(Those who go first)
(I have another suggestion)
How about this?
Do it in order of age,
from oldest to youngest, okay?
(Still these three men starts)
What if someone lashes wrong?
(Demanding an explanation)
(What if someone lash wrong?)
Wrong is wrong.
What... What else can we do?
If you lash too many times,
just shake the bell again
so the previous try
doesn't go to waste, huh?
Okay, I'll try.
(Yuning steps up)
I'll go.
Where can I go through?
Can I go from here?
(Choosing position)
Shoulders might be a problem.
Slowly.
(Super long)
This works.
He's so slim.
I'll go through this one.
(Liu Yuning chooses his route)
Okay.
I'll go first and catch you.
(Guo Jingfei goes first)
I'll go first. Okay.
Okay.
(I think it's okay)
I think this round we can make it.
Come on.
Can we make the loudest sound
before we start?
I feel so suffocated.
Come on!
Come on.
We will make it this round!
Will we?
Sure. Come on.
Three, two, one.
This round...
- We will make it!
- Come on!
(Round 2 begins)
Go.
(Let's go)
(Start at the same time)
Wait.
Let's redo this round.
Forget this one.
(Reset the time)
There's no need to waste this time.
Yes.
Let's start over.
Right.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
We will make it this round!
Come on!
(Round 3 begins)
(Start at the same time again)
Start over.
Forget this round.
This round...
Are you jumping rubber band?
You're hooking it again.
Listen to me.
Just now...
It wasn't right.
The stress was wrong earlier.
We will make it "this round".
The logical stress was wrong.
No.
The stress should be on "make it".
(We will make it this round)
It should be on "make it".
We will "make it" this round!
Okay, come on.
One, two, three.
We will "make it" this round!
(Round 4 begins)
Come on. You handle his pants.
You handle his pants.
I'll handle his upper body.
Don't rush.
Don't rush. Stay calm.
(Progress 1/8)
Who's next?
Yuning.
Don't rush.
Give him a little push.
Slowly.
Take it slow.
(Progress 2/8)
No rush.
His clothes.
(Gather)
Hurry.
Bottom.
Slow down.
Right.
Slowly.
(Progress 3/8)
You will go through this one.
This one.
(Will it succeed this time?)
(Exit: The tall main force is ready)
(Inside: The two main forces are ready)
Yes.
Lie flat.
(Using leverage)
Slow down.
Don't panic.
(Lifting with shoulder)
Slow down.
(Liu Yuning's shoulder,
Guo Jingfei's eyebrow)
(The height strategy is effective)
The dress.
Don't move.
Pass it over.
Lift it a bit.
Yes.
Okay.
(Progress 4/8)
(Totally exhausted)
(Strike your pose when the alarm sounds)
Okay.
(Your turn)
Your head.
Turn around.
Turn around. Right.
(Holding strong)
(Fighting)
(Keep carrying on the shoulder)
Slowly.
The dress.
(Who knows the feeling
of your arms coming back to life?)
(Progress 5/8)
(Time is running out)
You go first, Honglei.
(Rushing)
Don't rush.
Slowly.
(Progress 6/8)
(The last two)
(Lift)
(High knee lift)
(Focused protection)
(Suffered because
of the graceful figure)
Carry him
and send him over.
Come on.
(Earth Group's physical strength guy)
(Grabbing in a hug)
Go.
Okay.
(Grabbing in a hug)
(Progress 7/8)
(Graceful figure)
(Personal record is verifiable)
Don't rush.
Wait a moment.
Okay.
It's fine.
Listen.
(The last one)
Step on my shoulder.
Can't do that.
I can't.
It's fine. Come over.
Step here.
Get up.
(Decides to try on his own)
I think he can get through on his own.
(Feet can't touch the ground)
(Without hesitation)
Give me a hand.
Okay.
(Everyone comes to help)
(Push hard!)
No.
(Take off shoes and try again)
Slow down.
After you step,
just throw your whole body forward.
Don't try to stand steadily, okay?
(Progress 8/8)
Bring shoes over.
(Left us behind)
(Mission accomplished)
You must step.
After you step,
just let your whole body
go forward. Yeah.
Get some rest.
So awesome.
Since all paintings
have successfully escaped the frames,
next,
we will take a special vehicle,
a tuk-tuk,
to the Paris Fairground Art Museum.
We're free!
This game was really hard.
(Lei's compliment mode activated)
You were the best.
You have quick reflexes.
(Of course)
Of course.
(Want more)
Let's play a little longer.
What game should we play?
(Yili Yoghurt Chewy Lemon Challenge)
One person spins the wheel,
and the other calls stop
within three seconds.
Aligning the avatar
with the chewy lemon is a success.
Success within three attempts
wins the chewy lemon.
If all attempts fail,
the penalty is eating a real lemon.
(Confidence stems from self-assurance)
I find it okay.
- Okay.
- (Round 1.)
One, two, three, go.
- Failed.
- Counts as the first attempt.
- One, two, three, go.
- (Round 2.)
(Wen has a plan)
I can wait until it slows down.
That won't do.
(Playing tricks)
(Focused...)
(But failed)
No way.
I'll eat a real lemon.
(Gloating)
Let's do again.
(So sour)
- One, two, three, go.
- (Round 3.)
(Successfully hooked)
Impressive.
Such a team spirit.
Really fired up.
Cheers.
Celebrate our victory!
(Chewing)
(Peel and pulp)
The peel and pulp is great chewing.
Yili Yoghurt Chewy Lemon
is the best drink.
(Agree)
Yuwen is right.
Chewy lemon is just so good
that you can't stop.
(Addicted)
♪Forget about right and wrong♪
How are we supposed to sit?
Four on each side.
Am I driving?
You can't.
Those who get carsick
sit facing forward.
The others sit facing backward.
(A little cramped)
I don't get carsick.
(Door handle)
It's like a door handle.
Sit down.
The rafting, remember?
(The trouble of long legs)
During rafting, our feet were like this.
Right.
Tuck them underneath.
We were stuck.
Fill it up.
♪Summer breeze♪
(Singing anytime, anywhere)
♪Blowing through my hair♪
♪Telling me clearly that you love me♪
Next time, try singing softly.
Softly.
Like a whisper.
(Eyebrows straining)
♪Summer breeze gently blowing♪
Too much breath.
♪Summer breeze♪
Still need to make sound.
(Start practicing)
♪Summer breeze gently blowing♪
Sounds nice now.
Sounds good?
It sounds good like this.
Is that
half-air singing technique?
(Injecting air)
Half-air singing technique.
Yes. Very pleasant to the ear.
Like telling a story.
- Like talking right into your ear?
- Right. Like that.
It's like when you act
an emotional scene,
you have to use a breathy voice.
Is this really
a local vehicle from Paris?
It's for sightseeing.
Just like our rickshaw.
(Very straightforward)
Sightseeing.
For sightseeing.
This is my first time taking one.
So beautiful.
(Arc de Triomphe: On the Champs Elysees)
Look at the Arc de Triomphe.
(Sits at the center of
Place Charles de Gaulle)
(Napoleon had it built
to celebrate his victory at Austerlitz)
(A symbol of France
and a must-see in the city)
Triumph.
Triumph!
My camera angle seems
(Cameraman Lin is online)
to be shooting a kissing scene for it.
Right.
It's like a track.
Circular track.
The roads
go around it in a radial pattern.
Right.
Twelve avenues.
Yes.
Right next to us is the Champs Elysees.
That street over there.
That street.
Right.
Champs Elysees.
♪Champs Elysees♪
So nice.
So pleasant.
Really good.
Sorry.
How did I understand French?
(Is it an illusion?)
I think I understood French.
She made me stunned.
A foreigner said "sorry" in Chinese?
I thought I understood French.
Hello, boys and girls.
Why are you here?
(A surprise encounter scene begins)
(Spotting the highlight)
Looking at it this way,
why do you look so normal?
How come you guys aren't normal?
(What do you think?)
Look at the two of us.
Especially us two.
We're literally
straight out of a painting.
And you
also look like a waitress.
(Sirs, dining or lodging?)
Like a rag, right?
Let me wipe the table for you.
(Just smile)
(Road's tricky.
Sit steady and keep it safe)
(Snake-like walking)
Yo!
Wow!
Snake-like movement.
Driver, I'm precious.
I'm a famous painting.
(Too immersed, bro)
We're here.
We've arrived.
Thank you.
Okay. Thank you.
Is this it?
This is so cool.
(Over 1,500 antiques from 1850 to 1950)
Paris Fairground Art Museum
(It is more like a non‑stop carnival)
is known as "the most fun museum in Paris".
In 1996,
Jean Paul Favand,
an actor and antique dealer,
put his lifelong collection
of amusement park antiques
on display here
and opened it to the public.
Compared with traditional museums,
it's more like
a 19th-century amusement park
sealed away by magic.
It allows us to immerse ourselves
in the entertainment culture
of old France.
Three.
Two.
One.
Welcome!
I love amusement parks.
Thank you.
Welcome to the Fairground Art Museum.
You are all so eye-catching! Super nice!
It has many dresses hanging up there.
Look.
That's exactly
what an amusement park needs.
This is a century-old amusement park.
So nice.
It's quite pretty.
Pretty.
It's pretty in here.
So this is the Carnival Museum.
Okay.
You are now
at the Paris Fairground Art Museum,
a unique place.
(Natalie, Museum guide and performer)
Are you ready to join me
to swim in happiness?
Yeah.
We're ready.
Then follow me!
Let's go.
Swim over?
Swim over.
Only do breaststroke?
Let's play a game.
Look at this statue.
Look carefully.
Let's do the statue's pose.
Okay.
Statue!
(Very satisfied)
Thank you.
Okay.
Look at what she's holding.
What she's holding up
is a garland.
Garland.
Flower.
That's right, see what's
at the centers of the flowers.
At the centers of the flowers,
what do you see?
Gold.
No.
Gem.
Diamond.
No.
Light.
(Ultimate emotional value)
That's right, it's lights.
(In 1900, electricity was an emerging technology)
In 1900,
(They were used to catch people's eyes from afar)
fairgrounds were the first places to use electricity extensively.
A lot, really a lot.
Right now,
we will go in through this door.
Travel back to the past.
Okay.
(Where is this music coming from?)
Please follow me.
I need to blow this.
(Dancing with joy)
Warm-up exercise.
Okay.
Why dance?
(Doesn't understand,
but the body does it honestly)
I'm a bit tired.
A bit tired.
(Today's cardio goal met)
Do you want to see?
Come and look.
(Giant mobile fairground organ
Made by the Hooghuys brothers of Geraardsbergen, Belgium)
(It relied on punched cardboard to drive the performance)
This is an organ.
(It is the MP3 player of France's Belle Epoque)
This is a music box.
Music box.
A 1905 fairground organ.
This one.
Do you know what this is?
Sheet music.
Music sheet.
Please listen carefully.
Prick up your ears and listen carefully.
Let's make it play.
Start.
Very awesome.
It feels like a music box.
Yes.
Amazing.
A wind-up music box.
This is just like a music box.
The logic is the same.
But it's a more complicated mechanism.
Yes.
Now what we're going to play is
the Cafe Waiter Race.
Cafe.
What Cafe?
We'll go play Cafe.
(What magical thing is it now?)
Play pinball.
(Cafe Waiter Race game)
(Players toss balls into different holes
to move their little waiter forward)
Give it a try.
I have one more.
(Chen Xingxu reaches
the finish line first)
(The Swing Boat features a swaying hull
that simulates a boat ride on the water)
About to fly out.
Who hasn't played this?
Thank you.
It's not over yet.
Please follow me, quickly, over here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the highlight is here.
Right now,
you will see our museum's treasure.
Please turn around.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
Now lift the curtain.
The rotating bicycles.
This should be a very old one.
A unicycle.
(The Bicycle Carousel)
This is one of a kind.
(Made in Italy, and its facade was crafted by French artisans)
A fairground collectible.
Mr. Jean-Paul Favand
discovered
this bicycle carousel one day.
It was in a severely damaged state.
He spent a considerable amount of time
restoring it to working order.
It is now considered a true work of art.
It stands as a testament to that era,
bearing witness to the historic moment
when the bicycle was first invented.
At that time, there were more bicycles
in fairgrounds
than on the roads.
Yes, ordinary people can
rarely have the chance
to ride a bicycle.
And they saw them rarely.
Sitting on it, he had
a feeling
he had never experienced before.
The speed.
Now this bicycle carousel is 100%
calf-powered.
Human-powered.
Okay.
Let's ride it.
I think we can experience it.
I want to ride it too.
I just want to experience it.
(Looking for the right bicycle)
Which one do you want to ride?
(This one then)
I'll help you up.
It's so slippery.
(Everyone is on a bicycle)
This is magical.
I've learned something new.
We have only eight people.
Can we pedal this and make it move?
Well, we'll have to stand up
and pedal later.
We have to stand up and pedal, right?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Okay, start.
One.
Two.
A bit faster.
This is too fast.
(He had)
(a feeling
he had never experienced before.)
(The speed.)
Look at Guo Jingfei.
He's not pedaling.
(The feet off the pedals)
It's too fast.
Make it faster.
(Speed up)
Come on.
Make it faster.
Faster.
It's too fast.
Make it faster.
Come on.
Enough.
(Experience ends)
Happy.
I got a cold from the wind.
(The wind was too strong just now)
The wind was a bit too strong.
It made me catch a cold.
This is an antique.
This is something special.
This is really interesting.
It's quite thrilling.
And it is maintained to this condition.
Yeah.
Let's thank
our guide.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
Thank you for your participation.
Let me add something.
In all of Europe, our museum
has the largest collection
of fairground-themed artifacts.
We've always wanted
to share our passion
for these collections with everyone.
Today, for these collections
to be seen by more people,
we have to thank you.
Thank you for your eyes,
your smiles, and your joy.
Thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
Nice introduction.
Members of the Earth Group,
as the Escaped Paintings,
you've spent a whole day outside.
Now,
as night falls,
the museum is about to close.
You've received today's
(Elaborate)
final mission.
What?
(In the French film
Night at the Museum,)
(when the museum doors close,)
(the security guard's mission)
(is to find the escaped paintings)
(and return them to their places)
(to restore peace to the museum.)
Now, among you, there is one
(The guard must find all paintings)
security guard disguised as a painting.
(Round 1, 2 bullets, Round 2, unlimited bullets)
What the rest of you must do is
(Paintings must complete verification and avoid pursuit)
successfully evade this hidden guard's pursuit.
(After the 2 rounds,)
Once discovered by the guard,
(the surviving paintings on the field)
you will once again
(can jointly obtain 1 bullet to counterattack the guard)
be sealed back into the frames.
During the escape,
you need to find
a mirror
with the designated colored sticker,
(A companion's hand makes a phone gesture)
use a companion's hand to make a phone call,
and sing a love song
to prove you are still free.
Failing to complete
the verification action
will result in being sealed back
into the frame.
Furthermore,
in the first round of each game,
the guard
has two bullets.
In the second round,
it upgrades to unlimited bullets.
A painting hit by a bullet
will immediately
return to the frame.
After two rounds,
the surviving paintings on the field
can jointly obtain one bullet
to counterattack the guard.
Okay.
Let's draw for our roles then.
- Draw it.
- Let's.
(Role drawing
Who will become the security guard?)
(This round's security guard: Secret)
Honglei.
You stick with me first.
(Super proactive)
Let's not be alone.
I'm definitely not the guard.
You can't be the killer either.
Because you can't even
understand the game rules,
and you can't run.
(Is that even polite?)
Why is Xingxu standing over there?
Because I'm about to start.
(Testing)
You have a role?
I'm heading to a spot.
You guys aren't leaving.
Go go go.
(Initial spawn point)
Spawn point.
How scary.
Everyone, say something.
Friend in the sky, how are you?
I'm fine.
So scary.
I'm scared.
But the first step is
to ally with someone,
right?
(First to ally with someone)
Okay.
So I just need to complete my mission.
(Focus on the mission)
Prepare 20 love songs.
Who could be the killer?
(Curious about the role)
The killer is Liu Yuning.
Watch out for him.
Watch out for Song Qian.
Anyway, the smart ones.
So earlier, when I came up,
I wanted to ally with Honglei.
Because I knew
it couldn't be him.
(What kind of talk is that?)
He came right up to me
to form an alliance.
(The motive is questionable)
I think buddies,
girls,
ladies,
you won't hurt me.
So I still choose to believe,
except for that person in red.
I don't really trust him.
But I'm closest to him right now.
Attention, all paintings.
The valid mirror for the first round is
(This round's verification mirror)
a mirror with a red sticker.
Please, in front of the valid mirror,
(Cooperate to complete the action)
complete the designated verification action with a companion.
Please, in front of the valid mirror,
complete the designated verification action
with a companion.
This round, the guard has two bullets.
(The Painting Escape officially begins)
This one here has a red sticker.
(Believe in the power of belief)
If I were red-blue colorblind,
(Pointing to blue and calling it red)
could I treat it as a red sticker?
(Not allowed)
Alright.
So now I need to go find my companion.
I need to observe first.
What are you doing?
I'm looking for a mirror.
I'm looking for a mirror too.
Hey,
(Direct invitation)
Xingxu, come, follow me.
Wait, why?
I'm taking a wild guess.
Come, follow me.
Wait, I don't dare follow you right now.
(Cautious)
You and me.
I don't dare follow you
right now either.
Us two.
Xingxu, follow me. It's fine.
You follow me.
(Could Liu Yuning be the security guard?)
I think you're good.
Really?
Can I really trust you?
I think you're good.
No.
Don't touch me.
Xingxu, let's go together.
No.
Honglei,
(Running away)
I can't be alone with you right now either.
Xingxu, listen to me.
I'll listen to you, okay?
(I'm not picky)
I'll listen to you.
I don't really trust you, bro.
You're too proactive in this round.
(As if he is another Honglei?)
(Correct mirror)
Red one.
I saw one.
(Need cooperation to complete verification)
But you need someone to help you make the phone call,
right?
Yeah.
So you follow me.
No.
I think three will also do.
(Three as a crowd is safer)
Three people.
Three people is okay.
That works.
Okay.
One mirror can only reflect
one person at a time.
One person at a time, right?
Let's do yours first.
I'll go first.
You go first.
Let's do yours first.
(Hand gesture coordination)
A love song, right?
Yes.
Just sing one line, a full line.
♪You say you♪
You...
No, just kidding.
Hurry.
(Continue singing)
Just kidding.
♪Want to escape♪
♪But destined to settle down♪
(Verified)
Okay, good.
Let's go, follow me.
You two follow me.
Let's go together.
Hurry up.
The mirror will be gone soon.
Let's go.
The three of us cooperate.
(Three people forming a group)
(Qian and Nai reunite)
How about this? Ally with me.
Okay.
After we see it,
we'll first help the one
who saw it complete it.
Found it.
♪Give me a cup of forgetfulness water♪
(Singing across the distance)
- ♪In exchange for a night without tears♪
♪My heart is clear to see♪
(Cross-screen harmony)
♪Longing for a true love♪
(Verification successful)
Yuwen.
I have a red mirror here.
Can you help me verify?
Okay, can you help me verify?
But why are you being so kind?
Can I trust you?
You can.
You help me verify first.
Then we'll look for red mirrors
together.
Okay.
(Approaching)
Wait a second.
Yuwen.
Wait, can you not touch me?
Just be a little further away.
What's wrong?
How can we verify if I'm further away?
You stretch your hand over,
but don't you come over.
Let's just try
to avoid physical contact.
Okay, fine.
Alright.
As far as possible, okay?
I can see you from the mirror.
Don't make small moves.
(Forced perspective verification)
This is a good trick.
Okay.
A little closer.
Three, two, one.
(Guo Jingfei suddenly appears,
interrupting the verification)
Go.
(Change of plans, retreat)
You two.
I just saw you.
Neither of you is out.
So, neither of you is the killer,
right?
(Keeping distance)
Can I join your group?
(A team-up invitation)
Well, you guys can help me,
because I can't be the first...
Hard to say, bro.
(Trapped in a dead end)
You step back first.
You want to kill two at once?
Bro, you have two bullets.
Will you use them both on us two?
How did you corner us two
into this dead end?
Let's go find a mirror, bro.
(Running away at light speed)
Quick, find one.
Find a mirror.
Look for it.
(Rushing into the crowd)
Why are you running?
Running.
(Following closely)
It's really not me.
Because I can't even
understand the game rules.
How come he's not anxious at all?
Yeah, and he's looking by himself.
Like us two, we definitely
would try to help each other
find a mirror.
If he finds one,
who can make a call for him?
Have you completed it, Fei?
Not yet.
It's really not me.
I don't have a mirror yet.
Come here.
I have one here, come on.
(Choosing to trust Fei)
Okay, I'll help you first.
I'll verify you, no problem.
(Mysterious gesture)
♪As long as it's sincere♪
No problem.
Why are you poking my chin?
I'm just poking blindly.
Anyway, as long as my hand is in there,
that's fine, right?
Okay.
(Hesitated for a second and believed it)
Can you still verify me?
Sure.
Okay.
♪Longing for a true love♪
You're dead.
I'm just messing with you.
I was so scared.
You really scared me.
For real?
No.
(Verified: Chen Xingxu, Li Naiwen, Song Qian,
Sun Honglei, Liu Yuning, Lin Yi, Guo Jingfei)
Are there any more mirrors?
There's one outside.
Come on, I'll show you.
You scared me.
I took it seriously.
I'll verify you.
(You get what you ask for)
Thanks, Fei.
Sing.
(Again)
Your gesture is weird.
Sorry.
Wait a moment.
It's fine. Since he's making
this gesture, just sing.
(In broad daylight)
We're right here.
Yes.
Come on.
You sing.
♪You ask me how much I love you♪
You're dead.
What do you mean?
I'll expose myself
because I'm not afraid of you.
(Public self-exposure)
Just kidding.
It's fine, it's fine.
He scared me like that just now.
He gestured like this.
I was like, what is this?
So mean.
What? You're the killer?
(What is Guo Jingfei's role?)
(Escaped painting)
(Just loves to joke)
(Security Guard)
(Fully disguised Security Guard)
What? You're the killer?
I'm not.
(Just loves to play)
(Observing secretly)
I just think it's so fun.
(This round's Security Guard: Wang Yuwen)
All members are verified.
The second round starts now.
In this round, the Security Guard
has unlimited bullets.
(Round 2 rule: The Security Guard
has unlimited bullets)
The valid mirror
has a red sticker.
(This round's verification mirror: Red)
Why is it still a red sticker?
(Observing Painting's progress...)
♪If the heart is tired, tears dry up♪
(Verified: Liu Yuning)
Okay.
(This round, the Security Guard
has unlimited bullets)
Bye bye.
(Sun Honglei, Lin Yi,
and Guo Jingfei eliminated)
In this round, the Security Guard
has unlimited bullets.
(Using unlimited bullets
to instantly kill three)
(What happened?)
Three dead at once.
Really?
Come here.
For real?
Really?
(Still unable to accept it)
(Obediently follows)
Wait, wait a moment.
Is this real?
For real?
Get in.
I need to go in too?
Yes.
Hurry up.
Three dead at once.
(Turning around coolly)
You died a long time ago over there, right?
We're all dead.
We're now hidden here.
Wiped out in one go.
I'm dead.
I'm dead too.
(Still hasn't processed it)
Why are the three of us standing together?
Of the three of us,
I was the first to die.
But her killing action
was exactly the same
as when you scared me just now.
(Look at her, and look at you)
Just like that,
three of us were dead.
(Futile rage)
She's so fierce.
She waited for the last round
with unlimited bullets.
(Totally awesome)
Naiwen, come quickly
and do the mission with me.
Quickly, where's Naiwen?
(A little occupied)
Naiwen.
Hurry up.
(A rare chance for Qian)
Naiwen.
Come on, follow us.
I only trust Naiwen.
Where is he?
Naiwen.
I want to...
(Missed it)
Wait a moment.
Wang Yuwen.
You scared me.
You...
(Pretending to be calm)
She scared me.
Okay, come on.
Come over.
Let's do the mission first, come on.
Unlimited bullets.
Stay away from Wang Yuwen.
It's not me.
Actually, it's fine.
If you two don't complete the mission,
it's meaningless.
She's not pretending anymore.
No.
We two can definitely do it.
Honglei.
Coming.
You have to rely on someone.
Wait.
You guys...
(Public humiliation)
Three of them are...
The three of them are already silent.
Wang Yuwen.
So scary.
What's so scary about this?
This person is terrifying.
I can't even touch you.
What's so scary?
Why are you hiding?
(Excellent spectator seat)
What's there to hide from?
This is terrifying.
Yuwen.
She's not Mona Lisa right now.
She's a lot like
the one in Snow White.
You know,
the old witch.
(Front-row critique)
Old witch.
Yuwen.
Honglei, it's really not me.
I surrender.
How could I hurt you, Honglei?
Please, I surrender.
Honglei.
I'm such a kind child.
Would I ever hurt you, Honglei?
Honglei.
I'm such a kind child.
Would I hurt you, Honglei?
Stop it.
So terrifying.
So scary.
See, once she gets the killer role,
she even pins her hair up.
(Before and after the corruption)
Would I hurt you, Honglei?
She's so happy.
In this world, there has never been
so many people afraid of her.
She probably can't see me here.
I'll rest for a while.
It's quite cool.
(Missed again)
I have no face.
(Just like that, without looking back)
(Honglei got scared)
It's so scary.
Are there any more red mirrors?
Did you find one?
Didn't you find one earlier?
Honglei.
Oh no.
You're terrifying.
I'll definitely have nightmares, Yuwen.
Is anyone helping you?
(Are you all alone? Little Honglei)
No.
No one is helping you.
Xingxu, I see you.
So brazenly?
Are you showing your cards directly?
(Help me)
Yuning,
please help me.
It's terrifying.
(Already crying, please don't scare me)
It's so terrifying.
Yuning,
please help me.
What's wrong?
Help me quickly.
Quickly.
Go, let's go.
(Abandoning the mirror to escape)
Let's leave.
Just go.
Go.
Don't run toward me.
Don't come toward me.
It's so scary.
(The Girl Who Is Terrified)
(Mona Lisa's Sneer)
As long as they can't find a mirror...
(Stamina depleted)
Xingxu.
Quickly.
Come on.
(Target mirror)
Honglei.
It's here, right here.
(Line of sight blocked)
Under the wooden horse.
Honglei.
Come over and help Xingxu
complete the mission.
(Me?)
Why is she everywhere?
Careful, run slowly.
Please.
Goodbye.
(Security Guard: Wang Yuwen.
Chen Xingxu, Guo Jingfei, Lin Yi, and Li Naiwen eliminated.)
I'm dead.
(Only 3 paintings are free)
No.
Song Qian.
Do the mission quickly.
Did Yuwen try to kill you just now?
Yes.
She targeted me.
Hurry up and do the mission.
I already finished it.
Help me do a mission.
Okay, where is it? The mirror.
Here.
(Keeping an eye on the Sunflowers)
Wait a moment.
Honglei, be careful.
Quickly.
Here.
Hurry up.
What other love songs are there?
A love song, anything.
What?
♪The rooftop will catch fire♪
That's not a love song.
I'm willing.
♪For you, I am willing♪
♪To forget my name♪
(Verified: Girl with a Pearl Earring)
(The unverified: messy Sunflowers)
(There is one minute left)
(until the end of the second round.)
One minute left.
Wang Yuwen
is so terrifying.
Honglei.
We are the only ones left.
So terrifying.
Come here.
Let me make a phone call, Honglei.
No.
You have an incoming call.
Will you answer it, Honglei?
I'll sing you a love song.
♪Sing me a love song♪
Why are you still here?
Honglei.
Right.
It's useless for me to get him.
He hasn't completed the mission anyway.
Wait a moment.
Yuning,
come quickly.
Coming.
It's fine, I'll run for a while.
It's great that she's chasing me.
Come and chase me.
I don't need to chase Honglei
because he hasn't completed the mission.
That's true.
He'll be gone soon.
Okay.
(Didn't sing a full line of a love song)
♪With You All the Way♪
(Time's up.)
(Sun Honglei
did not complete the mission)
(and is automatically eliminated.)
(Sun Honglei is eliminated.)
(The second round is over.)
(From now on,)
(Rule activated: Surviving Paintings jointly obtain 1 counterattack bullet)
(the Paintings obtain one bullet)
(Escaped Paintings: Liu Yuning, Song Qian vs. Guard Wang Yuwen)
(to counterattack the Security Guard.)
(The situation is reversed)
I obtained one bullet.
(The girl is confident again)
(Slap the opponent with your palm,)
(and the opponent
is eliminated immediately.)
Slap the opponent with your palm,
and the opponent
is eliminated immediately.
Is this a dead end?
(Mona Lisa Cornered in the Restroom)
Come here quickly.
Who else is alive?
Just you two.
Just me and Yuwen?
Where is she?
Coming right away.
I'm scared.
You have a bullet.
What are you afraid of?
Where is she?
Two against one, it's fine.
Here.
Two against one?
We're on the same team.
Who else is there?
Me.
You're alive too?
Awesome.
Yes.
Here, take this weapon.
Give her a shot.
Okay.
Let's go.
Okay, let's go.
What's this for?
It's okay.
Let's go.
Slap her with your hand.
Where did she hide?
She's afraid of us now,
because there are two of us.
What are you doing?
I'll go out first.
Okay.
I'm so scared.
What are you afraid of?
I'm afraid she'll catch us off guard.
(Mona Lisa is more afraid)
(Face-changing skills)
She might
attack us.
Let's go back-to-back.
Walk this way?
Yeah.
We're so timid, us two.
Two against one, and we're scared.
Okay, it's fine.
Come, let's go in.
Why do we look so sneaky?
(Startled)
She's here.
Please.
Yuwen, come out.
Try to take one of us down with you.
I got her.
Alright, come out.
(The Security Guard is eliminated.)
(Game over.)
(Guard Wang Yuwen eliminated.)
Let's take her back, come on.
Take her back.
I'm sorry.
I didn't...
Bad girl.
No.
I didn't do anything just now.
Shut up.
(You have the right to remain silent)
You were just about to attack me.
How can you be like this?
No, I'm sorry.
I didn't do anything.
I trusted you so much, Yuwen.
I don't know what happened just now.
I was so strange.
I know, you were possessed.
Yes.
(Gentleness is my true color)
I'm not usually like that.
You exposed yourself too quickly.
I didn't have a choice.
Everyone was together.
You should have spilit us up.
I couldn't.
If I split you up, I would...
She's sweating from playing.
Actually, it's hard for the civilians.
Because it takes some time
to build trust.
(Calling me out?)
That's right.
(This round, the Paintings
escaped successfully.)
(Escaped successfully)
When I first started chasing Honglei,
I thought
even if I don't win,
this is still very satisfying.
(Full immersion experience)
Let me tell you,
I should be a veteran by now,
but for the first time, I felt fear.
Really.
(Captured Painting's accusation)
She came straight for me.
Would I hurt you, Honglei?
It has something to do with her outfit.
(Captured Painting No. 2)
She corrupted.
First, she stuffed me and Lin Yi
behind the curtain.
(Captured Painting No. 3, Captured Painting No. 4)
You know, we just...
A lot of information was lost.
(Captured Painting No. 5)
Time was tight, and so was the pressure.
The three of them
could only be squeezed behind a curtain.
Let's draw for roles for this round.
(Second round role drawing)
Nai,
(What are you thinking?)
how to "kill" in this round?
No, I'm thinking about love songs.
(Song library exhausted)
So you ran out of love songs.
Everyone, head to your
new spawning points for this round.
(Round two begins)
Song Qian,
is that you?
Let's team up.
Let's team up
(Song Qian's role: an escaped painting)
and go find mirrors.
Whoever sees one first
gets it,
and then we help the other find one too.
Okay, no problem.
Right?
(Initial points)
I'm a total civilian this round.
(Good Person Yu Ling returns)
I'm tired.
I'm a civilian.
(Escaped painting)
Is that you?
(The painting is confused)
Let's team up.
Why did you turn down my team-up offer
in the last round?
Why are you asking to team up now?
(The initiative has shifted)
Because I trust you.
You think I'm reliable, right?
I think you're handsome.
Okay.
(That hit the spot)
Okay, I'll agree to that.
Let's team up. Come on.
Okay.
Don't regret it.
I won't regret it.
Absolutely not.
Okay.
Naiwen.
Why did it take you so long to look?
Who?
You.
Looking at what?
Are you so nervous?
What words?
The words on that role card.
No.
I was just showing it to the camera.
I'm a Good Person.
But don't give me that.
You were acting weird just now.
Don't give me that.
Did those two lines really
need that much thought just now?
I'm a Good Person. I really am.
I really am a Good Person.
I wanted to catch the "killer" myself.
Okay.
We should
cooperate.
(Can Nainai be trusted?)
Qian,
join me.
You're not, are you?
Of course not.
Whoever took longer is the one.
(Listen to my analysis)
I was observing from the back.
Then who do you think it is?
Naiwen. He took a long time.
And Liu Yuning.
(Identity in doubt)
I saw both of them
took quite a long time.
Liu Yuning?
But he was just trying
to team up with me earlier.
(Live broadcast in the brain)
You're being very proactive right now,
coming to ask if it's me.
Then you probably are...
You know how to play.
I'm so scared.
I didn't observe.
But I think just now, Yuning
seemed like it but also
didn't seem like it.
(The seed of doubt has been planted)
Attention, please.
The valid mirrors for the first round
are the ones with a blue sticker.
(This round's verification mirrors: blue)
Are the ones with a blue sticker.
Let's keep our distance while walking.
I know where one is.
If you want to gain my trust,
you need to help me complete it now.
(Paid alliance application)
If you want to gain my trust,
help me complete it first.
No problem.
I'll help you complete it now.
Let's go.
I'm going with Chen Xingxu.
(Broadcasting to prevent being caught)
We're off.
Come on, let's cooperate first.
(Inviting again)
You scared me to death.
I trust you.
I am.
I'm a civilian.
(Torn)
I trust you.
Is there a mirror?
(Pulling him away)
Yes.
Over here.
(Target mirror)
It's blue, right?
Come on, help me complete it first.
(An old-fashioned love song)
♪You sit up front on the boat♪
♪I'll keep pace on the shore♪
(Verified: Li Naiwen)
Okay.
How is it?
I trust you now.
(Conditional trust)
Because I trust you.
(Unconditional trust)
You help me complete it.
No problem.
I'll make a call for you.
(Super cooperative)
♪If the heart is tired, tears dry up♪
♪This deep love is hard to let go♪
(Verified: Liu Yuning, Li Naiwen)
Okay.
Okay, no problem.
(Song list Ctrl+V)
♪If the heart is tired, tears dry up♪
No problem?
Put it down.
♪Must one understand romance♪
(Verified: Liu Yuning, Li Naiwen,
Chen Xingxu, Lin Yi)
Okay.
♪Shouldering all the problems alone♪
(Verified: Liu Yuning, Li Naiwen,
Chen Xingxu, Lin Yi, Wang Yuwen.)
Okay.
Honglei.
Here.
Come quickly.
Why are you
so slow and sluggish now?
♪With you along the way♪
(Verified: Liu Yuning, Li Naiwen, Chen Xingxu, Lin Yi, Wang Yuwen, Sun Honglei)
♪Even if it hurts, I'm willing♪
Okay, verified.
Liu Yuning, it's you this round.
You guess people...
You really read people accurately.
(Is Liu Yuning the Security Guard?)
You see people crystal clear.
Who did she see through?
She saw right through me.
She said it's me.
I've already been verified.
Lin Yi, don't go.
Where are you going?
Let's not have
too much physical contact.
No contact.
Yuwen, I noticed a detail just now.
The earliest one
to leave the scene was Xingxu.
(After drawing roles, left first)
The one who left first was Xingxu.
Why was Xingxu in such a hurry to leave?
(Raises Honglei's suspicion)
You couldn't do something
right in front of people, could you?
Right?
You left the earliest.
(Is Chen Xingxu the Security Guard?)
It's fine.
You expect me to vouch for you?
I'm very suspicious of you.
I didn't say that.
Let's go quickly.
The aura is a bit strong.
There are already two
sitting over there.
Two are sitting there?
What does that mean?
(Rule: Eliminated players
are forbidden to talk with others)
(What exactly happened?)
(Five minutes ago)
It's fine if we team up together.
Come on.
Come on, awesome.
Come on, help me.
I'll help you find one later. Come on.
Goodbye.
It's you?
Don't speak.
Let's go.
I'm sitting here.
Why are you sitting here?
(Playing dead)
What's going on?
Who?
Already sitting here.
(From Wang Yuwen's perspective:
2 "dead" + 1 "alive")
Already sitting.
(Excuse me?)
Wait.
There are already two
sitting over there.
Wait.
Two are sitting there?
What does that mean?
(Right under their noses)
Honglei and I have alibis.
Right.
(When it happened, four were outside)
Those two have alibis too.
Then it's either Naiwen or Lin Yi.
(Unable to defend himself)
Do you have alibis for each other?
Naiwen is definitely not.
(Giving Naiwen a Good Person card)
Why?
I checked him.
He definitely isn't.
(Confident)
How did you check him?
I can't tell you.
(Unconvinced)
Round one is over.
Round two begins.
This round, the Security Guard
has unlimited bullets.
(Unlimited bullets unlocked)
The valid mirrors for this round
(Everyone spreads out)
are the ones with blue stickers.
Honglei, there's a mirror over there.
Let's go quickly.
Quickly.
Quickly, let's go.
I'm so scared.
I won't talk. Don't worry.
I respect the game.
But I didn't expect you
to deceive me.
I'm just too trusting of people.
(Earth Group's honest person)
I think it's Lin Yi.
(Honest person No. 2)
Really?
The way he looked at me
just now was off.
I remember just now inside,
at the beginning,
I saw one at the starting location.
But I'm not very daring to go inside.
Fei, you can move freely?
(A chance has come)
I'm stretching my legs.
(Waiting for the right moment to act)
But I don't dare to be alone, Honglei.
(Requesting protection)
Can you follow me?
(Following closely behind)
(Unable to make a move)
Yes, better to move in pairs.
(Waiting for another chance)
Who left?
Weren't you sitting there?
What's wrong with me moving around?
(Interrupting my plan)
Then it's you, right?
Then it must be you.
What are you afraid of?
Soon, eight guns will be aimed at you.
(Hellish mode on)
Look, they're all wary of you.
They're all in pairs.
It's hard for me to make a move.
(Very tricky)
I can only wait for them to come over.
Find a place to hide.
Catch them off guard.
You better give them
a surprise attack.
That's the only way.
I'm too kind.
Five-minute countdown.
Unverified paintings will be out.
(Prey locked on)
Yuning, do the mission first. Yuning.
There's one over there.
What color is it this round?
Blue.
Blue?
Goodbye.
(Security Guard: Guo Jingfei.
Song Qian and Chen Xingxu are out)
(No more hiding)
An ambush?
Ambushing is really ruthless.
You ambushed me.
Did you find a mirror?
Quick, help me.
(Successfully verified)
♪Longing for a true love♪
Found it.
(Successfully verified)
♪Oh baby, say a little more sweet talk♪
There's one over there. Hurry.
I just saw it.
♪The deeper my love for you♪
♪The more my heart aches♪
(Successfully verified)
Honglei, sing quickly.
Sing quickly.
Let's go quickly.
Let's go.
It really isn't me.
Goodbye.
(Sun Honglei out)
(Sadly losing a teammate)
You guys quickly find a mirror
and help me complete it, okay?
I know.
You find it first.
I'll help you.
Don't run.
Goodbye.
(Wang Yuwen out)
Is it over already?
Yes.
It scared me to death.
You must hang on until the end.
The last two people.
You two are out?
Dead.
Both of us are out.
You're out too?
No, I'm "alive".
Then wait for the end.
Okay.
Well,
the problem is
I haven't finished the mission.
(Can't find a companion,
the mission is in jeopardy)
Goodbye.
(Liu Yuning out)
You still dare to be alone?
One more left.
One more left, Lin Yi.
Round two is over.
The paintings gain
one counterattack bullet.
(Li Naiwen and Lin Yi vs. Guo Jingfei)
Three more are left?
Everyone, as long as you use your hand
to touch the opponent's body,
you can eliminate them.
(Ambush set)
I touched you first.
I touched you.
(Nainai touched first)
(Successfully escaped)
(Guo Jingfei out)
Did you counter-attack?
Yes.
Nai, impressive.
I was there all along.
I was hiding there all along.
Where's Lin Yi?
(Still lying in ambush)
Hunting time.
(Serpentine movement)
The paintings escaped successfully.
(What happened to the hunt?)
Game over.
(Burned for nothing)
He finally showed up.
Naiwen is so awesome?
So cool.
Actually, even if we had touched
each other at the same time just now,
it'd have been a one-for-one trade.
Right.
I was really frightened by Fei.
As soon as I came out,
I turned my head and saw a big face.
He came straight at me like this.
He was like a goofy roe deer, you know?
He could have run away.
Once I pressed on his face...
He froze.
It was just too scary.
My soul bolted first.
Two goofy roe deer.
Yuning also froze.
He didn't run.
(The moonlight of Paris does not belong)
(to the world inside the frames.)
(When the midnight bell tolls,)
(they must return to the frozen)
(postures and expressions.)
(But don't feel sorry for them,)
(because the wind remembers
the way they ran,)
(the Seine River remembers
the reflections they cast,)
(and the night of Paris)
(will remember)
(this wonderful night for them.)
(Next Episode Preview)
Your ultimate mission today
is to complete a fashion show.
Tickets for sale?
Can we sell the tickets?
Next,
let's test the team's
internal chemistry.
Twist.
Start twisting.
Now,
on the left side of your chest.
Is this okay?
Not okay.
It's okay.
Your thumb and index finger.
Take them out. Yes.
Place them at the corners of his mouth.
(Which team will win in the end?)
Now,
go prepare for your big show.
I think
we don't necessarily
have to buy clothes.
We can buy some curtains
and drape them over ourselves.
You're right.
It might not even fit me.
Pair it with a silk scarf.
What tie goes with a black shirt?
Do you want a tie or...
or a silk scarf?
I want a tie.
The countdown
to the fashion show begins.
I've seen shows,
but I've never hosted one.
I've basically never even watched one.
This is the design for the stage.
Where is the audience area?
I can't understand it at all.
Let's first think of a story
to tie all things together.
We can change clothes here, right?
Come on, let's walk now.
Okay.
Let's just walk.
(Stay tuned
for the Earth Group's big show)
(Wow The World, show schedule)